<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JBake</title>
    <link>http://jbake.org</link>
    <atom:link href="http://jbake.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>JBake Bootstrap Template</description>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <pubDate>Mo, 25 Jul 2016 18:14:11 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mo, 25 Jul 2016 18:14:11 +0200</lastBuildDate>

    <item>
      <title>Top 3 Reasons to Get Your Digital Commerce Summit Tickets Now</title>
      <link>http://jbake.org/blog/2016/test.html</link>
      <pubDate>Di, 12 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">blog/2016/test.html</guid>
      	<description>
	&lt;p&gt;Digital Commerce Summit is three months away, and we&amp;rsquo;re all very excited about this inaugural event. It&amp;rsquo;s happening in Denver, CO on October 13-14, 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re a digital entrepreneur, or are interested in getting into the business of creating and selling digital products, this is right up your alley.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But you&amp;rsquo;re going to want to act fast, because the price is going up this month. Let&amp;rsquo;s quickly run through the most compelling reasons to sign up before that happens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. The Speakers&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regardless of other factors, the quality of a business conference is determined by the speakers and what useful insight they bring you. Our agenda is stacked with actual entrepreneurs who walk the talk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fact that they&amp;rsquo;re also great teachers is an amazing benefit as well. You won&amp;rsquo;t get lost in jargon and &amp;ldquo;inside baseball&amp;rdquo; references.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll learn from people like Rand Fishkin of Moz, Joanna Weibe of Copy Hackers, Laura Roeder of Edgar, and Chris Ducker of Youpreneur &amp;hellip; plus many more high profile entrepreneurs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, your favorites from Rainmaker Digital will be presenting as well &amp;mdash; Jerod Morris, Pamela Wilson, Sonia Simone, and Chris Garrett. I&amp;rsquo;ll be there too, but don&amp;rsquo;t let that deter you. :)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our integrated agenda assures that you&amp;rsquo;ll depart from Denver with a clear picture of your path forward. While one great idea is worth the investment, you&amp;rsquo;ll do much better than that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. The Entertainment&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re known for throwing great parties. The networking, relationships, and deals that happen thanks to like-minded people enjoying themselves together is just as important as the education.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year we&amp;rsquo;re adding a new element &amp;mdash; an exclusive performance by alt rockers CAKE on Thursday evening, October 13. The band has delivered hit after hit over the years, including The Distance, Never There, Love You Madly, and Short Skirt/Long Jacket, and this is going to be an amazing show at the Paramount Theater (which is also the conference venue).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll kick things off with an opening reception the evening of the 12th and end the conference with an epic closing party on the 14th. Stay tuned for more details on that Friday night event, because it too will be something special.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. The Price&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re with me so far, then this is the important reason to act now. The price of registration is going up to $995 on July 28, 2016.&lt;br/&gt;Why wait to pay more? We hope to see you in Denver!&lt;br/&gt;Register for Digital Commerce Summit today.&lt;/p&gt;
	</description>
    </item>

  </channel> 
</rss>
