<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JBake</title>
    <link>http://jbake.org</link>
    <atom:link href="http://jbake.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>JBake Bootstrap Template</description>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <pubDate>Fr, 19 Aug 2016 09:03:19 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fr, 19 Aug 2016 09:03:19 +0200</lastBuildDate>

    <item>
      <title>How To Evaluate A Business Idea</title>
      <link>http://jbake.org/blog/how_to_evaluate_business_ideas.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fr, 22 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">blog/how_to_evaluate_business_ideas.html</guid>
      	<description>
	&lt;h1&gt;How To Evaluate A Business Idea&lt;/h1&gt;
	</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 3 Reasons to Get Your Digital Commerce Summit Tickets Now</title>
      <link>http://jbake.org/blog/2016/test.html</link>
      <pubDate>Di, 12 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">blog/2016/test.html</guid>
      	<description>
	&lt;p&gt;Digital Commerce Summit is three months away, and we&amp;rsquo;re all very excited about this inaugural event. It&amp;rsquo;s happening in Denver, CO on October 13-14, 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re a digital entrepreneur, or are interested in getting into the business of creating and selling digital products, this is right up your alley.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But you&amp;rsquo;re going to want to act fast, because the price is going up this month. Let&amp;rsquo;s quickly run through the most compelling reasons to sign up before that happens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. The Speakers&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regardless of other factors, the quality of a business conference is determined by the speakers and what useful insight they bring you. Our agenda is stacked with actual entrepreneurs who walk the talk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fact that they&amp;rsquo;re also great teachers is an amazing benefit as well. You won&amp;rsquo;t get lost in jargon and &amp;ldquo;inside baseball&amp;rdquo; references.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll learn from people like Rand Fishkin of Moz, Joanna Weibe of Copy Hackers, Laura Roeder of Edgar, and Chris Ducker of Youpreneur &amp;hellip; plus many more high profile entrepreneurs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, your favorites from Rainmaker Digital will be presenting as well &amp;mdash; Jerod Morris, Pamela Wilson, Sonia Simone, and Chris Garrett. I&amp;rsquo;ll be there too, but don&amp;rsquo;t let that deter you. :)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our integrated agenda assures that you&amp;rsquo;ll depart from Denver with a clear picture of your path forward. While one great idea is worth the investment, you&amp;rsquo;ll do much better than that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. The Entertainment&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re known for throwing great parties. The networking, relationships, and deals that happen thanks to like-minded people enjoying themselves together is just as important as the education.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year we&amp;rsquo;re adding a new element &amp;mdash; an exclusive performance by alt rockers CAKE on Thursday evening, October 13. The band has delivered hit after hit over the years, including The Distance, Never There, Love You Madly, and Short Skirt/Long Jacket, and this is going to be an amazing show at the Paramount Theater (which is also the conference venue).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll kick things off with an opening reception the evening of the 12th and end the conference with an epic closing party on the 14th. Stay tuned for more details on that Friday night event, because it too will be something special.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. The Price&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re with me so far, then this is the important reason to act now. The price of registration is going up to $995 on July 28, 2016.&lt;br/&gt;Why wait to pay more? We hope to see you in Denver!&lt;br/&gt;Register for Digital Commerce Summit today.&lt;/p&gt;
	</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to find business ideas aka identify business opportunities</title>
      <link>http://jbake.org/blog/how_to_find_business_ideas_aka_how_to_find_business_opportunities.html</link>
      <pubDate>Di, 12 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">blog/how_to_find_business_ideas_aka_how_to_find_business_opportunities.html</guid>
      	<description>
	&lt;!--
1. GOAL

&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt; HEAD

&lt;!--
 Writing GPS

 1. GOAL
 We  want to drive awareness to our blueprints for finding business ideas, because we want to  help our customers and earn money with it.

 2. REFRAME
 We  want to drive awareness to our blueprints for finding business ideas
   so what?
 Because you need not a brandnew unique business you should rather go for a business idea
   so what?
 You need a business opportunity get your dream become dream
   so what?
 Otherwise you have to forget about your dream  of an own business

 Instead of hunting for brandnew unique business ideas you should concentrate on business opportunities for you passion to fullfill your dream of an own business.
 We help you with you with our business ideas

--&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Business ideas? Rather look for business opportunities The 7 steps&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There many myths about starting a business. One is that you need business idea. With good people mean, it&apos;s something brandnew and unique.&lt;br/&gt;In reality many of these ideas fail, because execution matters not just the idea. Brandnew ideas are difficult to bring to market, as people not activly looking for the problem of their problem. So rather looking for the genious idea rather find a great business opportunity. Business opportunities are everywhere, but you have to digg for the gold. We will show ho to start today by following our steps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simple list your passions and knowledge/skill set:&lt;br/&gt;Look for your &quot;Sweet spot&quot; as Joe Pulluzzi&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://contentmarketinginstitute.com/content-inc/framework-sweet-spot/&quot;&gt;http://contentmarketinginstitute.com/content-inc/framework-sweet-spot/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;E.g.&lt;br/&gt; Passions:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Traveling&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Soccer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skills:&lt;br/&gt; - Organizing stuff&lt;br/&gt; - Teach other people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now combine the skills with the passions:&lt;br/&gt; Taveling-organizing stuff&lt;br/&gt; traveling- teach other people&lt;br/&gt; Soccer-organizing stuff&lt;br/&gt; soccer-teach other people&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Check what people search on google with autocompletion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;You just type the keywords for your passion then you start with a, b, c...&lt;br/&gt;You write down what you find.&lt;br/&gt; E.g. travel and work&lt;br/&gt; soccer illustration&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;=======&lt;br/&gt;We want to drive awareness and interest on our blueprint to find business opportunities, because I want to earn money with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;REFRAME&lt;br/&gt;&quot;We want to drive awareness and interest on our blueprint to find business opportunities&quot;&lt;br/&gt;&quot;so what?&quot;&lt;br/&gt;&quot;Because you think you need an idea to start a business, but you need to find to business opportunities based on your skills&quot;&lt;br/&gt;&quot;so what?&quot;&lt;br/&gt;&quot;Without an business opportunity you can go the next step&quot;&lt;br/&gt;&quot;so what?&quot;&lt;br/&gt;&quot;You are not able to realize your dream&quot;&lt;br/&gt;&quot;so what?&quot;&lt;br/&gt;&quot;You have to stop dreaming about own business&quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;To get your dream come true you need to find business opportunity for your passions instead of thinking of a business idea. Business opportunities are everywhere, but you need to digg for them. We will show you ho to find the opportunities with our blueprints.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;SEEK OUT DATA AND EXAMPLES&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://articles.bplans.com/top-startup-mistake-6-ideas-vs-opportunities/&quot;&gt;http://articles.bplans.com/top-startup-mistake-6-ideas-vs-opportunities/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.quora.com/Whats-the-difference-between-an-idea-and-an-opportunity&quot;&gt;https://www.quora.com/Whats-the-difference-between-an-idea-and-an-opportunity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ask on quora.com &quot;?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ORGANIZE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;WRITE TO ONE PERSON&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;PRODUCE THE UGLY FIRST DRAFT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;WALK AWAY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;REWRITE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;GIVE IT A GREAT HEADLINE OR TITLE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAVE SOMEONE EDIT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;ONE FINAL LOOK FOR READABILITY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUBLISH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maybe a infograhic &quot;5 Myth about business idea&quot;&lt;br/&gt;--&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Business ideas? Rather look for business opportunities. We will show you how&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stop believing these top myths about business ideas&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pan for the gold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;blockquote&gt;
        &lt;blockquote&gt;
          &lt;blockquote&gt;
            &lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;db2c3327e7af9a837a063c94f65710ede654cfed&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/blockquote&gt;
          &lt;/blockquote&gt;
        &lt;/blockquote&gt;
      &lt;/blockquote&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
	</description>
    </item>

  </channel> 
</rss>
